# **Robert Wrana**

# Summary

Full-stack Web Developer with 3-4 years of experience in the software industry. Technology of choice for creating client web/hybrid applications is Vue.js with Quasar Framework and for server applications is .NET Core / .NET 5. Eager to learn new and improve existing skills.

## Skill

- JavaScript (TypeScript)
- Vue.js (Vuex, Quasar Framework)
- Java (Spring Boot)
- MS SQL Server
- PostgreSQL
- Couchbase
- Git

- C# (.NET Core, .NET 5, Entity Framework Core)
- Angular(Kendo UI, NGXS)
- HTML5
- CSS (SCSS)
- React

# **Experience**

Front End Developer - 09/2017 to 05/2019

Hiwe IT, Čakovec

- Worked on implementing web client applications for ERP systems.
- Implemented reusable table component that extends the functionality of a library Tabulator
- Skills: JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS

Bachelor's Degree Final Project - 03/2018 to 07/2018

#### Multi-criteria Decision Making Web Application using the Analytic Hierarchy Process

- Developed a web application for multi-criteria decision making using mathematical method called Analytic Hierarchy Process (AHP)
- The core of the application:
  - graphical modeling hierarchy of criteria and their weights implemented using hierarchy of diagram components
  - o creating or importing list of data
  - applying decision making algorithm
- Skills: C# (ASP.Net Core, Entity Framework Core), MS SQL Server, JavaScript, React, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS

#### Full-Stack Developer - 06/2019 to 04/2020

#### Hiwe IT, Čakovec

- Implemented Spring Clean Architecture Project Template that will be used in every project
- Server application template (Spring Boot):
  - o inspired by principles of Clean Architecture
  - implemented logic for easier report creation using Jasper Reports implemented using façade pattern
  - o implemented logic for export/import CSV / Excel files
  - implemented logic for Spring Security
  - o implemented logic for Spring Data for Couchbase NoSQL database
  - o implemented logic for saving files as a document (JSON) or as a system file
- Client web application template (Vue.js, Vuex, Quasar Framework):
  - implemented reusable component for handling forms with various types of inputs inside a table's rows – QDataTable (Live Demo)
  - o implemented mixin for creating validation functions from *validate.js* (with fluent api) object for easier application of validation logic
- Skills: Java, Spring Boot, Couchbase, JavaScript, Vue.js (Vuex, Quasar Framework), HTML, SCSS

#### Full-Stack Developer - 04/2020 to 07/2020

#### **Factory X**, Pribislavec

- Upgraded legacy Angular configuration (Webpack) to Angular CLI for better development experience
- Reimplementing legacy Angular code using better software architecture and principles
- Skills: JavaScript, Angular, Kendo UI, NGXS (state management library), .Net Core, Entity Framework Core, MS SQL Server, HTML, CSS

#### Full-Stack Developer - 07/2020 to 01/2021

#### **Hiwe IT**, Čakovec

- Improved previous Spring Clean Architecture Project Template by removing spring dependencies from service layer so that domain and service layers can be sharable with an android application
- Setup library <u>PipelinR</u>, which is an implementation of mediator pattern, for service layer
- Implemented validation, logging, performance middlewares
- Implemented dynamic vuex module for handling authentication and authorization with different behaviors for different types of session tokens (JWT, refresh tokens, replaying failed requests caused by session timeouts, etc.)
- Skills: Java, Spring Boot, Couchbase, JavaScript, Vue.js (Vuex, Quasar Framework), HTML, SCSS

## Master's Degree Final Project - 10/2020 to 02/2021 Generic System for Developing Process-oriented Applications that Support Document Management

- Web application is a generic workflow engine, it has been implemented in a way it
  allows users to define custom workflows for many business use cases. It works just
  like a finite state machine, workflow has states and every state has data and actions
  which triggers a transition to another state of a workflow.
- For every state of a workflow, users can design custom user interfaces like forms and texts. For that use case, I've created separate component called <u>QElementTree</u> (<u>Live</u> <u>Demo</u>) for building custom user interfaces using Quasar Framework UI components.
- Skills: C# (.NET 5), Entity Framework Core, JavaScript, Vue.js (Vuex, Quasar Framework), HTML, SCSS

## **Education**

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science: **Software Engineering and Computer Information Systems** – 2018 - **Faculty of Electrical Engineering and Computing,** University of Zagreb

Master's Degree in Computer Science: **Software Engineering and Computer Information Systems** – 2021 - **Faculty of Electrical Engineering and Computing,** University of Zagreb